uyow.com 2012-04-09

# www.uyow.com » Privacy

**Privacy policy**

Uyow.com is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains the type of information Uyow.com collects through its website and what Uyow.com does with it. Please read the following privacy policy carefully before using the Uyow.com website. If you use the Uyow.com website, you will be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy. This policy may change from time to time so you should check it frequently. Uyow.com does not attempt to determine the identity of any Uyow.com user by analyzing Web usage paths.

 **What Information Do We Collect?**

From time to time we may request that an entity making application for an account with Uyow.com provide us with certain personal information (such as their name, email address, etc.) in connection with various services offered on our site. We do not collect any personal information except when an individual specifically and knowingly provides such information. When we request information, we explain how this information may be used and give you an opportunity to request that the information not be used for those purposes. We also give you an opportunity to opt out of future communications from us.

 **Cookies**

For account management purposes and like most sites, Uyow.com uses cookies. Cookies are data files stored on your computer that identify you as a unique user. Cookies enable us to track user trends, preferences and patterns to better understand our user base and to improve the quality of our service. Most browsers permit users to refuse cookies or to be notified before a cookie is accepted. You can visit our site without using cookies.

 **Links to Other Sites**

Uyow.com contains links to other sites. These sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. Since we do not control these sites; we are not responsible or liable for the privacy practices or content of such sites.

 **With Whom Do We Share Information?**

Uyow.com may share non-personal and non-personally identifiable information about our users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. However, we only divulge aggregate information, such as how often the average user visits Uyow.com. We will not share personally identifiable information with any third party without your express consent.

 **Consent and Changes to this Privacy Statement**

By using our site, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this privacy statement and to our Terms of Service. Uyow.com may decide to change this privacy statement from time to time. When we do, we will post the changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies,[ click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).
